quiz_data = [
    [{
        "question": "What data type is '2.54'?",
        "choices": ["int", "float", "string", "boolean"],
        "answer": "float"
    },
    {
        "question": "What data type is 'True'?",
        "choices": ["int", "float", "string", "boolean"],
        "answer": "boolean"
    },
    {
        "question": "What data type is “5”",
        "choices": ["int", "float", "string", "boolean"],
        "answer": "string"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a valid variable name?",
        "choices": ["_2", "money$", "3", "variable name"],
        "answer": "_2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a valid variable name?",
        "choices": ["int", "True", "name", "if"],
        "answer": "name"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a valid variable name?",
        "choices": ["break", "false", "and", "in"],
        "answer": "false"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is an INVALID operator?",
        "choices": ["+", "/", "**", "!"],
        "answer": "!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the evaluation of 6**2?",
        "choices": ["error", "36", "3", "8"],
        "answer": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which in-built python method is used to take a user input?",
        "choices": ["in()", "inputs()", "input()", "user()"],
        "answer": "input()"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a valid variable assignment?",
        "choices": ["in  = input(“Enter a number: ”)", "number == 3", "amount = $25", "sum= 3 + 5"],
        "answer": "sum= 3 + 5"
    }
    ],
    [
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a valid list?",
        "choices": ["(‘1’,’2’)", "{‘a’, ‘b’}", "[‘a’, 1]", "[a, 1]"],
        "answer": "[‘a’, 1]"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the string ‘Python’, which letter is index 2?",
        "choices": ["y", "t", "p", "o"],
        "answer": "t"
    },
    {
        "question": "If list = [2, 3, 4, 5], what is the output of list[1]?",
        "choices": ["error", "1", "2", "3"],
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "If list = [2, 3, 4, 5], what is the output of list[:2]?",
        "choices": ["[2,3]", "[2,3,4]", "2,3", "4"],
        "answer": "[2,3]"
    },
    {
        "question": "If list = [1,2, 3], what is the output of list*2?",
        "choices": ["[2, 4, 6]", "[1, 1, 2, 2, 3, 3]", "[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3]", "error"],
        "answer": "[1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3]"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a valid way of printing using the f strings syntax?",
        "choices": ["print(f”printing in python with a {variable}”)", "print(“\f printing in python with a (variable)”)", "print(f”printing in python with a [variable]”)", "printf(”printing in python with a {variable}”)"],
        "answer": "print(f”printing in python with a {variable}”)"
    },
    {
        "question": "If list = [2, 3, 4, 5], what is the output of list.append(1)?",
        "choices": ["list = [3, 4, 5]", "list = [2, 3, 4, 5,1]", "list = [1, 2, 3, 4, 5]", "list = [1]"],
        "answer": "list = [2, 3, 4, 5,1]"
    },
    {
        "question": "If string = ‘314159’, what is the output of string.count(1)?",
        "choices": ["1", "2", "3", "error"],
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "If list = [2,3,1,4,1], what is the output of string.remove(1)?",
        "choices": ["[2,1,4,1]", "[3,1,4,1]", "[2,3,1,4]", "[2,3,4,1]"],
        "answer": "[2,3,4,1]"
    },
    {
        "question": "If string = “python string”, what is the output of string.remove(‘t’)?",
        "choices": ["[“py”, “hon”,  “s”, “ring”]", "“pyhon spring”", "[“py”, “hon s”, “ring”]", "[“pyhon”, “sring”]"],
        "answer": "[“py”, “hon s”, “ring”]"
    }
]
]